

Highly technical computer engineer with proficiency in several computer languages, industry experience. A blend of analytical and organizational skills provide a springboard for problem solving solutions and a strategic course of action whether in a team or individual setting.

EDUCATION

University of Akron - Akron, Ohio

GPA: 3.593

Bachelor of Science - Computer Engineering with Cooperative Education May 2016

Bachelor of Science – **Applied Mathematics**Dean's List: 2011 – 2016 I Tau Beta Pi: Member

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

Computer Engineer

January 2016 - Present

Akron, Ohio

CTIGoodyear Tire and Rubber Level 1 Team

- Create and maintain code, utilizing Oracle Pro*C, used in Goodyear plants that coordinates individual machines in factory automation
- Integrate new technologies, like Apache ActiveMQ and Camel into existing system infrastructure
- Traveled on site to Goodyear facilities to provide support, implement new software, and advise in projects to ensure smooth installations
- Maintain and update websites that provide reporting and configuration for the Level 1 systems using PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS, and Javascript
- Supported customers and helped troubleshoot any issues that were reported

Software Engineering Intern

May 2013 – December 2015

BGI-LLC Akron, Ohio

- Created new features and improved functionality using C++, Qt, Python, and JavaScript.
- Worked as part of the test team maintaining test procedures for the new software, writing new procedures as necessary.
- Analyzed data through the creation of algorithms that detect different types of events using physics and linear algebra.
- Lead assigned projects creating new functionality starting from inception, through construction, and ending in review and release.
- · Assisted in the SBIR Phase II project.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

PROFICIENT LANGUAGES: C/C++, Python, HTML/CSS/JS, PHP, SQL

KNOWN LANGUAGES: C#, Java, Matlab

ADDITIONAL PROJECTS: Github: www.github.com/linkian209



4264 Bridgewater Pkwy, Apt 302 Stow, Ohio 44224

lan.jeffrey.koyote. drake@gmail.com

(330)-957-4587